We'll be right back.
Showdown between cooks.
Sanji versus Ramen Kenpo.
Like I said, this guy is mine.
You go on ahead.
I'll catch up with you two later.
Remember, above everything else, our priority right now is to save Robin.
That's impossible!
I won't let you pass through!
I'm letting the high-quality floor!
Is he going to bring out the ramen noodles again?
Ramen beans!
Those are sharp!
Damn it!
Let's head over on the roof.
Right.
We'll leave it to you then, Sanji.
Best of luck!
Go, go, go, go!
They're go, go, go, gone!
But I suppose that's no big deal, because the person waiting for them in the next car is
one tough customer!
Nero!
He's the latest addition to CP9, an assassin for justice!
Those two are dead meat!
If there's one thing that Nero loves to do, it's kill!
Go, go, go, go!
Ah!
Flinchy.
Shoot!
Pow!
Huh?
Oh, the wind carries my name from Sniper Island far away.
When I take aim, it's straight and true.
This would be a whole lot easier if we knew which car Robin was in.
I could infiltrate from the roof and be done in a snap.
Stop muttering and go already, you stupid slimy squid king!
Who are you calling a slimy squid king?
Uh-huh.
Hmm.
Slimy squid?
Sticky octopus.
Squid octopus, whatever, just hurry!
Bikini guy!
I've got a brilliant plan.
Listen very carefully.
This'll take forever if you keep dodging me like that.
I told you, I'm in a hurry here.
Okay then.
Fine.
Ramen Kenpo Noodle Slicer!
Hehehehehe!
Let's see how you like this!
But escape late!
T-T-T-T-T-T!
Not only did you disrespect my beautiful attack, you kicked me 10 times, didn't you?
Not only did you disrespect my beautiful attack, you kicked me ten times, didn't you?
Actually, it was twelve times.
Hey, you! Are you secretly super strong or something?
It's not really a secret. Maybe you're just super weak.
Super weak? Not even my old man would say something like that to me!
How dare you! I'm Wansi! I wouldn't let you get away with this!
Rude! Besides, I was simply distracted by your swirling eyebrows.
They make me dizzy! That's why I fell for your attack.
Still, you're a good fighter. Too bad you look weird.
Hey, you freak! You're in no position to call anyone weird-looking!
After that failed attack, I feel like I need to prove myself, so I'm gonna show you something amazing!
This is why I was chosen to escort those criminals!
Ramen Kenpo's Secret Technique! Ramen Kenpo's Secret Technique!
Beat the dough! Pull the dough! Beat the dough! Pull the dough!
Uh, what the hell is all that?
It's my incredible edible combat uniform!
Ramen's formal suit! Now, fight! Go, go, go, go!
Go! The secret of this Ramen Kenpo Technique is controlling the three moving noodles at will!
See?
Bastard. How dare you disgrace food like that, you weirdo!
My speed, my power, and my special abilities! I'm at a different level now in all those areas!
Yeah! If showing you isn't enough, I'm gonna boot it in you!
Go!
Just shut up already and get on with it.
But prepare yourself, because I'm gonna make you eat every last one of those noodles.
Question.
Who are you? What are you doing up here?
The officer in charge of the third car, a four powers master, and a new recruit in CP9, the sea weasel, Nero.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, I'm under specific orders not to kill you.
You know, you being one of our most important criminals and all.
All right, that's one half. Now tell me what you're doing up here on the roof of this train.
If you'd just waited inside, I would've come to you.
Well, how was I supposed to know that? You may have tried to cheat and skip right past this car.
My, my, my. That's rather cautious of you.
But in your line of work, you always got to keep your guard up, right?
By the way, what's that weird-looking thing there behind you?
That was a dirty trick.
Of course it was!
They don't call me the King of Water 7's underworld for nothing.
Hey, hold on. Where did Luffy run off to?
Beats me.
Beats me? Come on, you know that, idiot. What if he fell into the water or something?
Oh, slippery.
That's impossible. I mean, he was right here up until a few seconds ago. Right, Chopper?
What? Oh, sure. This is Luffy we're talking about. That doesn't mean anything.
I'm worried because he was here and he's not here now.
Maybe he's stuck in Rocket Man's chimney. It happens, right, Zoro?
Oh, sure. And choking you happens, too.
Just wait, Robin. We're coming for you!
Oh, and Usopp, too.
I'd like to welcome you to the wonderful world of ramen kinpo!
That is the lamest power-up ever.
Go, go, go! Here I come!
Ramen kinpo!
Pork punch fake attack!
That's the same useless punch from before, only bigger.
Go, go, go!
Habitada!
Ah, damn it! I'm stuck in this stupid thing!
Oh!
Go, go! Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go! So what do you think?
My ramen kinpo attacks are pretty impressive, aren't they?
It's kind of hard to look cool when your arm and leg are buried in noodles like that.
And now I believe it's time to pay you back for all those kits you gave me earlier.
What?
What the hell are you getting dizzy for, you idiot?
You were trying to make me woozy using your freaky eyebrows again, weren't you?
Bad move!
What? You're gonna pay for that!
You're gonna pay for that!
Go, go, go!
Ah, damn it!
I can't pull my arm or my leg out.
It's impossible to fight back like this.
Here comes my noodle soul crest!
Ah!
Want some more?
Kiss?
I'll do my helping!
Ah!
今一つの光を見つけた気がして 追いかければ逃げてゆく未来は落ち着かない
何度も何度も立ち止まりながら 笑顔と涙を積み重ねてゆく
どんなに闇の深い夜でも 必ず明日は来るから
また会いましょう
Crunchystage
クランキが見つけた NEAR
私から покigaにある
クランキのパイロス
You